{
    "id": "ed67de773a4744ec92024e6ee57dd5ae",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………………. his poor vision, he reads books.",
            "description": "In spite of is a preposition. It is followed by a noun / ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "However",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0186ec36c0354b10abcc1099ff16b726"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… difficult the problem is, he can solve it quickly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07f0498c7cf5493a8956ea480c338f39"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. his repeated requests, she refused to help him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8e98c34532994f6882be0c0d53dd4838"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… working hard, she failed.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is followed by a noun / ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "However",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "30b42f6c41c547858d61bb74bbdaea5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. his popularity as an actor, he could not win the election.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is followed by a noun / ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "However",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9dd0c6b1a5c04226aae07fc66ec84e66"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. cold it is, he always goes swimming.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "91f0b91384f646efa6d171ad1826f4b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. you obey my orders, you will be dismissed.",
            "description": "Unless is similar to if not.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Until",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a33f6f0b770843edb5eea10c96e3c78e"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… you invite her, she will not come.",
            "description": "Even if is used to connect two contrasting ideas. It refers to the present or future.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Even if",
                "Even though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3f6673a21bb54c339218283269c7e9c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. it is expensive, he is determined to buy it.",
            "description": "Even if is used to connect two contrasting ideas. It refers to the present or future.",
            "answers": [
                "Even if",
                "Even though",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0b3c78ff54234dd689386c73ef0aed17"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. he is rich, he leads a simple life.",
            "description": "Though is similar to but. It is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "If",
                "Even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "383b5eb9c6414d27ab50f9b61789e93d"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. she was cooking, her clothes caught fire.",
            "description": "While can be used to connect two actions that happen simultaneously. ",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "Since",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "901149c1040f4f8baa2af932aa45b73a"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. he was not there, I spoke to his mother.",
            "description": "As is used to give the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "While"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0ce20a71cdf44c869f15d3dc93eae60e"
        }
    ]
}